- Sorry he woke you.
- Oh, it wasn't him.
Was I snoring again?
I thought it was a low-flying jet.
- Thanks for playing with him.
- I don't mind.
I had to get up early anyway to drive
home and get changed for work.
Yeah. He's a good kid.
You know, I'd like to stay at your place
but when I have Benjamin, it's...
I know. It's fine.
You know, you should be
careful, lady.
I could still make
an honest woman of you yet.
You actually could.
Did you hear about
last month's policy change?
Oh, yeah. No more sanctions
on office relationships.
Yeah. Read the e-mail.
Right. As long
as there's no rank issues.
Right. So, I, uh...
I couldn't date Lisbon.
- Right. But do you wanna date Lisbon?
- No. Ooh. God, no. I just...
No.
They're even letting agents
get married.
"That's awesome."
- You wanna shower first?
- Oh...
- You go.
- All right.
Lisbon. Good.
We're going to Napa. You drive.
- Homicide bulletins?
- Hot off the press.
A John Doe in a duck pond awaits.
Well, that sounds like a case
for local authorities.
Bingo.
Napa. Okay, wait a minute.
That's Sheriff McAllister's jurisdiction.
You wanna go and investigate
a Red John suspect.
Investigating is your thing. I'd just like
to get to know him a little better.
Shall we?
Gardening crew found
the body submerged in the pond.
Doesn't look like he was in the
water for more than a few hours.
There's a contusion
on the back of the skull.
I'm guessing someone
caught him from behind.
What was he doing behind a church
in the middle of the night?
Any personal belongings?
No wallet or cell phone.
Just a money roll in his front pocket.
$32 in small bills.
Hey, Jane?
Care to offer your opinion?
These ducks love muffins.
- Very helpful.
- Look at 'em go!
I see the cavalry has arrived.
- Sheriff McAllister.
- Agent Lisbon. What, uh...
What brings your crack team
to our little slice of heaven?
Oh, you know, any excuse
to get up to wine country.
Well, we always welcome the help
but I expect I can handle this one.
Well, to be honest, it was, uh...
it was me that wanted to come out here.
- Is that a fact?
- Well, more of a feeling.
I think there's more out here
than meets the eye.
- How so?
- You don't feel it?
- Mm, no.
- What's your take?
- On what?
- Our friend.
Well, let's have a look.
"One five six."
You suppose he's repping his code?
Area code 1-5-6 is reserved
for telemarketers
so I'm guessing no.
Well... he's kind of
a slack-looking fella.
Gloomy, even for a corpse.
You know, cheap clothes,
no muscle tone.
Uh, sedentary low-income job.
- Sounds right.
- Your turn.
The tread on his shoes
wrap up around the heel
to prevent the heel from slipping
like those of a serious race car driver
or a delivery man that likes
to pretend he races cars.
Couple that with the roll of small bills
found in his pant pocket...
Pizza delivery man.
Could be Mexican.
Or ribs.
Could be.
But, uh...
you don't detect the faint scent
of oregano about him?
That's a leap.
What do you think?
Well, he's not as dumb as he looks.
Well, is he Red John?
- It's too early to say.
- How do we find out?
- I need to be alone with him.
- Well, that would not be wise.
What's cookin' in here?
Spot any clues?
No. Well, just that hammer up there.
You see it?
Is that blood on the hitting side?
Could be.
I'll call forensics.
- Fellas?
- "Yeah."
- We need a little help...
- Did you see that?
He did not wanna go
up that ladder.
Uh, didn't the psychiatrist's office say
that Red John was afraid of heights?
That's very astute, Lisbon.
Well observed.
They'll join us
when they're done outside.
Yeah, I can't wait that long.
Sheriff, would you mind going up
the ladder for me?
You want me to climb all the way up there
in these pointed toe boots?
That's a job for sensible shoes.
- It would be a big help.
- I got it, boss.
- Thank you, son.
- Hey, boss
Cho got a D.M.V. hit
on the victim's prints.
His name is Larry Kincaid,
46, clean record.
No. Doesn't look like blood.
I think it's paint.
Thanks, Rigsby.
Kincaid lived in Vacaville
and worked as a pizza delivery driver.
What was the victim
doing in Napa?
His boss said he was here
for his niece's wedding tonight.
Stacey Bonner. The rehearsal dinner
was here last night.
All right, you two stay in the area
and look for witnesses.
We've got a wedding party
to find.
Use the table to help you swirl.
The table's your friend.
You look so sexy
when you do that.
This draws oxygen into the wine
to bring out the aroma.
Who cares what it smells like?
Let's drink.
Excuse me. Uh, uh, is this
the Bonner-salas wedding party?
I'm Stacey Bonner.
Can I help you?
Yes, I'm agent Teresa Lisbon
with the CBI. This is Patrick Jane.
We found a body behind the Bella Vista
wedding chapel this morning.
It's a member of your party.
His name is Larry Kincaid.
Uncle Larry?
Oh, no.
Well... don't everyone cry at once.
My wife's brother was something
of a courtesy invite.
He's a nice enough guy, but...
a little off, socially speaking.
Okay.
Uh, you're the bride's father, I take it.
And, uh, where's your wife?
She's resting back at the hotel.
She came down with a migraine
last night.
Poor uncle Larry.
Mom's gonna freak out.
- It's okay, cariña.
- The wedding is ruined!
- What happened to him?
- That's what we're trying to find out.
- Can I see the body?
- Suzie, that's not very appropriate.
This is life happening.
We can't shut our eyes.
- So... can I look at it?
- No.
Who was the last person
who saw the victim alive?
All of us.
After the rehearsal dinner
we all hit up the big party tent.
- The wedding Pavillion.
It's the big tent by the chapel.
We ran out of wine, and Larry offered
to make an alcohol run.
I'm Mr. Salas.
Roberto's my son.
- Did uncle Larry ever come back?
- No. But we weren't surprised.
It felt like he was looking
for an excuse to leave the party.
Yeah. It's like he was a ghost
before he was a ghost.
Angel, you're such an idiot.
He was her uncle.
I'm sorry, baby.
He seemed like an okay guy.
I'm not crying
about uncle Larry.
It is the wedding day.
Hey, we're still gonna get married,
right? Right?
- I guess. But it's all so... sordid.
- Yeah.
Lisbon said this was the last room
the victim was seen alive in.
Well, it's gonna be
a beautiful wedding.
Eh, I can think of better ways
to spend good money.
Oh, yeah? Like what?
A new leather sectional?
No.
Okay, how'd you guess?
I used to dream about having
a Cinderella wedding.
You did?
You never said anything.
Ah. It was a long time ago.
I suppose it all seems silly now.
Police.
Who's in here?
Step out slowly.
Don't shoot.
Set it down.
- Hands behind your back.
- It's not what you think.
What's this?
Laxatives in the wedding cake, huh?
That's a cute move.
- What's your name?
- Oscar Salas.
The groom's brother.
Why'd you wanna ruin
your brother's wedding, Oscar?
- Why not?
- You don't like his fiancée?
Twitter freak.
Completely self-obsessed.
They all are. Children who need
constant feedback.
Just wait until they try that cake.
I am dying to read that tweet.
What about uncle Larry?
He seems cool.
At least he doesn't follow the pack.
Did you know he was murdered last night
after the rehearsal dinner?
- No.
- Any idea who might wanna hurt him?
Yeah. Angel.
My brother's best man.
He talked trash about Larry
all the time.
I think he sent him
text messages, too.
- What was your beef with the victim?
- No beef.
- We heard you didn't like him.
- You heard wrong.
I didn't have no opinion of him.
Barely knew the guy.
We also heard you harassed him
with text messages.
That's not true.
- How about you show me those texts?
- I'm not giving you my phone.
I can have a court order here
in 30 minutes.
Only then, I'll be looking at you
as a suspect.
"Hey, Larry, any word yet
from your boss?"
"I could really use the work.
Thanks, buddy."
- He was helping you get a pizza job?
- I need work. So what?
- You get the job?
- Nope.
Did you leave the wedding tent
at any point during the after party?
No, I was there till the end.
Ask anyone.
And Larry was long gone
by the time I left.
Thank you for coming,
Mrs. Bonner.
Did you happen to see
your brother leave the party?
No, I, uh...
I had a headache.
I left the party early and walked back
to the honeymoon suite.
Why were you
in the honeymoon suite?
We're paying for this wedding.
What was the victim doing
at the party?
The usual.
Standing... watching.
To be honest, I felt sorry for the man.
What was your relationship
with the victim?
Larry's my fiancée's uncle
so as far as I'm concerned,
he's my blood.
But weird blood, you know?
Do you know of anybody who may
have wanted to harm the victim?
Nobody really felt strongly enough
about him one way or the other.
He just kinda... floated along
like family flotsam.
That was his strength, you know?
The power of social invisibility.
I think I could've loved him.
Did he talk to anyone
at the party?
Yes. My son's friend Charlie
from college.
Did you know Roberto
went to college?
First in the family.
Well, I was pretty toasted.
But I think Larry was talking
about a new rifle.
Said he bought it
to defend himself.
Rifle? Are you sure?
The victim doesn't have
any record of gun ownership.
I think he was just trying to fit in.
You know, be one of the guys.
Same reason Larry offered to go
on a liquor run for us.
Did you see the victim
leave the party?
"I don't speak English."
"Excuse me."
Somebody in that wedding party
had to have seen something.
Love is in the air, Lisbon.
These two families
are about to be married.
They're not gonna turn on each other
without a push.
What kinda push?
If we're gonna learn who killed uncle Larry
then we need to clear the air.
That means no more playing nice
for the happy couple.
We need some honesty.
- Who's not being honest?
- Well, you, for starters.
- You're the groom's sister, I take it.
- And my bridesmaid.
Yes, that was a lovely gesture
but you put her in a very awkward
position because she resents you.
- No, I don't.
- Yes, you do. Be honest.
Do you resent me, Rose?
You talk down to my brother!
You're always correcting him.
- That's not true. When has she ever...
- Not now, Roberto.
Rose, are you mad at me because
I paid for your bridesmaid dress?
- You didn't pay for my dress.
- You don't work in retail.
Now she's doing it to me.
Stacey was an English major, chica.
She just sounds superior.
Chica? My daughter
is not your housemaid.
Hey. She speaks English.
Can we all show
some respect here, please?
- We're a family now.
- Yes, one big, happy family.
Is that why you hooked up
with the bride's mother at the after party?
Hmm? What was that?
You said that your wife
had a migraine last night
which is the enablers' code
for "drunk".
And today, she can't look
the groom's father in the eye.
That's why she wasn't
at the wine tasting this morning.
You made a move on my mom?
Why are you blaming Papi?
Maybe your mom's the adulterer.
- Adulteress.
- Stop correcting him!
- Yeah! I see it now.
- Okay, shut up!
This is my wedding day,
and I will say and do whatever I want.
And what I want...
is to cancel this wedding.
Life. Happening.
Stacey, you don't mean that.
You guys have been planning this for months.
I flew in from Florida to be here.
You're all on your own.
Nice push.
Ah, something good will come
outta this. You'll see.
- Can we go back to Napa now?
- Please.
Groom's brother said that neither side
of the family approves of the wedding
but they're both pretending
like they do.
- Not anymore.
- I followed up on that rifle tip.
According to bank records, uncle Larry wrote
a personal check for one two weeks ago.
We need contact information
for the firearms dealer.
A private rancher sold it to him.
James Harris. I have an address.
The victim said he brought a rifle
to protect himself.
Let's find out from who.
Rigsby, you're with me.
I'll run background checks
on the invitation list.
I thought you were supposed to solve
a crime not, uh, destroy a wedding.
Well, I'd say the killer did that.
I'm prepared to marvel at your insight.
Who's the killer?
Still working on it.
Really? I'm surprised. I'd have...
I'd have thought you'd have him
in cuffs by now.
Oh, I hate to disappoint you.
Jane. Mrs. Bonner would like
to have a word with you.
You were right.
Before I left the party,
Mr. Salas and I shared a kiss.
A drunken, mistaken kiss.
Uh, where did this, uh, inebriated
smooch take place?
- Behind the chapel.
- Did you see anything here by the pond?
No, but we heard a splash
around midnight.
Did you hear any...
screams or sounds of a struggle?
I should've gone to help him.
It wouldn't have mattered. It seems
he was killed someplace else.
The body was just dumped here.
Hiding the body until
after the wedding in the pond
which is not such a great hiding
place, I would think. A little too public.
Bella Vista.
"Beautiful view" in Italian.
Where is this, uh, Bella Vista?
Through the trees.
Wow.
Now this is a place to dump a body.
Take a look. Huh?
Killer hauls the body to the pond.
Just a little bit further
and he could've dumped it right here.
He's right. Nobody's finding
anything down there.
Come over here, fella. Have a look.
Yeah, I'm familiar with the view.
Uh, tell us what we're looking at.
- "Sheriff, what's your location..."
- Excuse me. I'm gonna take this.
- Yeah I'm close, I'll head...
- Strike two. You believe me now?
Hey, Cho, you think
I'm a marrying type?
You proposed to your baby mama.
Well, yeah, but every kid deserves
two parents.
I was talking about Van Pelt.
- You knock her up, too?
- No.
So why are we talking about this?
Well, you clearly missed
the departmental memo.
They changed the policy
on office relationships.
Don't have to lay low anymore.
Hmm. Good for you.
We could even get married
if we wanted to.
Ah.
That's it? "Ah"?
She wants to get married
and you don't want to.
No. Maybe.
No. I don't know.
What do you think I should do?
You wanna make it my fault?
Okay, you're right.
It's my call.
You're on private property.
- CBI agents. You James Harris?
- That's right.
You sell a rifle to a man named
Larry Kincaid about two weeks ago?
It's quite possible.
I'd have to check my receipts.
It's a violation of state law for you
to sell firearms without a license.
- What are you hiding in the barn?
- My private arsenal.
Open the door, please. Keep your hands
where we can see them.
If I recall
Larry bought one of these.
A genuine 1840 Springfield musket.
It's rigged up to fire blanks now.
You're a civil war re-enactor.
That's right, field commander
for the Napa Valley Cumberland guard
156th regiment.
We got a battle next week in fort point.
That must be what the "156" meant
on the victim's shirt.
What victim?
Larry was murdered last night
behind the Bella Vista Chapel.
Very sorry to hear that.
You know of anyone who may have
wanted to hurt the victim?
Oh, God, no. No.
Larry was a harmless sort.
Quiet, but... a good soldier.
His loss is gonna leave a real whole
in our little community.
You break it, you buy it.
Oh, please, don't stop praying
on my account.
Oh, I'm not praying.
Texting.
In church.
Isn't that a sin?
I hope not. I make my living
with my thumbs.
I'm, uh, sorry for busting your wife.
It's not the first drunken kiss
she's shared with a man that wasn't me.
And I'm sure it won't be the last.
Do you have any idea
who killed her brother?
I believe it was someone
from the wedding party.
No. No, you're wrong.
No one had any reason
to kill uncle Larry.
It would be like... killing a llama.
Why would you?
They spit?
What do you do for a living?
I'm a speculator.
- I look for undervalued assets.
- What kind of assets?
Oh, artworks, islands...
anything I can buy low and sell high.
Last month I found a first-edition
Coverdale Bible at a church auction
printed in 1535.
I was gonna do a reading from it
at the wedding.
How much is that worth?
- Oh, uh, half a million.
- Wow.
For an antique bible.
- Where is it now?
- With a private security firm.
They were gonna deliver it here
for the wedding tonight.
Might as well just sell it now.
- Agent Van Pelt.
- Grace, I need your help.
It is imperative that our young lovers
go ahead with the wedding as planned.
Good luck with that.
You ruined a girl's wedding.
Yes, and I lack the putty
to spackle those emotional wounds.
That's why I'm calling you.
- I have putty?
- No, you have life experience.
Use it to convince the bride that her
"happily ever after" begins tonight.
Really?
Jane is feeling really badly
for what happened in the bull pen.
He shouldn't.
This was never going to work.
He did me a huge favor.
Your families
don't want the marriage.
Mom says I'm too smart
for Roberto.
And my dad is worried he won't be able
to take care of me.
And Roberto's parents just want him
to marry a nice catholic girl.
What do you want?
I want Roberto.
But...
It's too complicated.
So you're gonna throw it away?
Look...
I had someone I wanted to spend
the rest of my life with.
"But..."
"Staying together would've ended
my career."
"So I let him go."
What happened?
Oh...
I got engaged to someone else.
That ended badly.
So I shut down a little inside.
"Closed some doors to feel safer.
But..."
the problem is with every passing year
you close more doors.
Until eventually...
you wonder if anyone will ever
get inside again.
- That's really tragic.
- Yeah. Well...
that's why I keep the dress.
- Your wedding dress?
- I know. It's crazy, right?
But...
It reminds me of who I was...
Naive. Maybe a little foolish, but...
"full of hope."
I'm afraid if I destroy that dress...
I'll forget what hope feels like.
What are we gonna do
about McAllister?
Well, until I get some alone time with him
I'm not gonna draw any conclusions.
Well, he's avoided heights twice.
If Red John is acrophobic,
why would he tell my shrink?
To gain her trust
so he could steal her file...
which he did right before he killed her.
Guess what?
We're getting married. No hard feelings.
Well, I think that's a great decision.
Congratulations.
You... of course, you know
we will have to attend the ceremony
just in case uncle Larry's killer
reveals himself.
- Okay.
- Uh, you should follow us.
- The courthouse closes.
- Courthouse?
What about your big Napa wedding?
It's a waste, but, I mean, what can we do?
I can't find a priest.
I canceled him this morning.
And we only have the chapel
for two more hours. So...
Well, you know, it turns out that
I am, in fact a certified wedding officiant.
- I can marry you.
- Oh, my gosh.
- You're a lifesaver. Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
It would be my pleasure.
- Oh, you are not legally ordained.
- Yeah, I've never used it.
But I always thought
it was a handy thing to have.
- I don't believe you.
- I swear.
I could marry you off in a minute.
Hey, Ron.
Don't tempt me.
- "Sheriff McAllister."
- Yeah, it's Patrick Jane.
"What can I do for you, Patrick?"
Well, I'm at the chapel.
We have a break in the case.
How soon can you meet me here?
"Real soon."
Funny thing, I, uh, saw your car
in the lot and I was just coming to find you.
I didn't hear you coming.
You move quietly.
Well, it's an old habit.
I've been a hunter most of my life.
Really? What do you hunt?
Anything with a face.
Game is game, right?
You hunt?
Me? No.
No. Too squeamish. I...
I couldn't handle all the skinning
and the gutting.
Sure, yeah.
Clean and quarter a kill.
- It takes some stomach for that.
- And a certain bloodlust.
There's a grain of truth in that.
So you got a break
in the duck pond killer case?
Well... less a break, but, uh, more a plan.
I'm gonna reveal the killer tonight. And
I need you and your people to just hang back.
No problem.
I truly appreciate you making
my job easier for me.
You look great.
Thank you, Wayne.
Jane thinks our man's gonna try
to sneak out of the reception.
We need to be there.
I'm gonna follow him.
What if he's too cautious to make
a move while we're here?
If he's in the reception tent
for more than two hours
Jane wants you to create
some sort of distraction.
He thinks it'll encourage him out.
- What kind of distraction?
- You know what?
- Don't worry. I can handle this.
- Great. Great. Let's split up.
"For this thing shall a man leave
his father and mother"
"and cleave unto his wife"
"and the twain shall become
one flesh."
Whoa. That sounds messy...
but beautiful.
Thank you, Mr. Bonner.
Reading from the very rare
and valuable Coverdale Bible.
Scripture... tick.
Rings... we've, uh, we've done that.
- Have you ever done this before?
- Have you?
- Yes. I'm married.
- What's next?
- Kissing.
- That's what I thought.
Okay, um...
If there are no objections...
- Nope.
- Okay.
By the power vested in me...
by a mail-order ministry, I...
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
Roberto...
you may kiss the bride.
Be careful.
I'll, uh...
I'll guard that for you, if you'd like.
You wish.
Mr. Bonner trusted me to lock this away
in the priest's room for the reception, so...
step back, son.
Excuse me?
- Thank you. Try the cake.
- Oh, thank you.
It's been two hours and nobody's going
anywhere near the exit.
- We need a distraction.
- Okay.
How do I look?
- Fine. Why?
- Good.
Excuse me? Is this on?
Yeah.
Uh, excuse me, ladies and gentlemen
if I can I have your attention,
for, uh, one second, please?
I'd like to offer one more toast.
I'd like to thank Stacey and Roberto
for making me realize
just how important it is to protect a dream.
I didn't protect my dream.
To be honest, I, uh...
well, I didn't know how.
But what can you do when you meet
the right person at the wrong time?
Do her anyway!
Well, yeah, that works...
for a while. But...
eventually you say things
or don't say things.
You, uh, make more mistakes
than you can count.
And in the end
well...
things fall apart.
- Is this your idea of a distraction?
- Trust me.
Now if you're lucky
you might find each other again.
But there's too much history
and heartache
to ever find your way back
to that dream.
At least that's what I thought.
I'm hoping... I was wrong.
Grace...
will you marry me?
Well, say something. This is real.
Yes, Wayne.
Of course I'll marry you.
Target's on the move.
Oh, that was easy.
- How'd you know I'd be here?
- You know, the big fight at the CBI
you were the only one that wanted
the wedding to go ahead as planned.
Ergo, you were the guilty party.
Guilty? I was just checking on the bible.
I didn't do anything.
- You killed a man.
- What?
Oh, Charlie, stop.
You're just embarrassing yourself.
There's only one way you could Jimmy
a dead bolt with a putty knife.
You sawed through the bolt.
So you snuck out of the party but...
somebody caught you
in the act, didn't they?
Charlie?
What are you doing here, Larry?
I came to swipe the priest's wine.
We ran out at the party.
Pretty smart, huh?
Uh, what are you doing here?
Is that a saw?
You're gonna steal
the bible, aren't you?
You know how much
that thing is worth?
Larry, it's insured. All right?
Mr. Bonner will get his money,
and we'll get rich.
That's right, I'll cut you in.
Okay, you'll never have to deliver
another pizza in your life.
I kinda like delivering pizzas.
- I'm going back to the party now.
- Larry, wait!
Well, you're not gonna
tell them, are you?
No, I...
I'm just going back. Bye.
I don't suppose you wanted to kill him
but, uh, if wishes were horses
and all that...
And you not being from around here
you didn't know about the cliff
so you threw the body in the pond.
I suppose you took
the wallet and I.D.
because you wanted to make it
look like a robbery.
You can put down
the putty knife now.
Whatever.
I'll leave this up to my lawyers.
Just...
- don't make the handcuffs too tight, okay?
- Oh, no, no.
- I don't do the cuffing...
- Jane, move away!
- Charlie, put the gun down.
- My dad died in jail.
I'll take my chances
on the outside, thank you.
You know, if you just let me go
I'm sure they'd be happy
to open the dialogue with you.
Charlie, stay calm.
You don't wanna go down this road.
No, you don't.
Get away from me!
You wanna live?
Get me outta here.
Upstairs, now! Go!
Charlie, think about what you're doing!
- What's through the door?
- No idea.
I'll cover it. Set up an exterior perimeter
with Rigsby and Van Pelt
and call for backup.
Keep moving.
Uh, yeah, I'd... I'd love to, Charlie
but without wings...
On the roof. Now!
- We're getting outta here.
- Okay.
Whoa!
You know if there's
a-a way down from here?
- We're gonna find a way down.
- Yeah, that's what I was afraid of.
Uh...
Hey!
Drop the gun.
Now he's talking directly to Jesus.
Where... where did you come from?
The church keeps an extension ladder
for tree trimming.
Don't look down.
Bad place for the spins.
Give me your hand.
Let's go.
Good thing I ignored your request
to stay away, huh?
Guess I just felt obliged
to keep an eye on you.
- Yeah. Why?
- Truth is, I didn't trust ya.
The way you forced your way
onto the case here...
it almost seemed like you had
a hidden agenda.
Ah, well, sometimes
I give out mixed messages.
It's one of my many failings.
- It looks like everybody's okay?
- Sure.
He saved my life
out there on the roof.
My pleasure.
I'm at your disposal anytime.
I'll see you two downstairs.
Hey, get it out! Get it out!
I didn't see that coming.
I hate those things.
- You're not hurt?
- Oh, I'm fine, Lisbon. Fine.
Well, you missed all the action,
you know.
Oh, I did? Did you not see me
out there on the roof?
- That was some action.
- This is different.
It looks like we're gonna be spending
a little bit more time
in Napa than we expected.
Really?
Join hands and face each other, please.
Grace, you'll begin.
Repeat after me.
- I, Grace...
- take you, Wayne...
to be my husband.
To have and to hold
from this day forward...
for better or for worse
for richer or for poorer
in sickness and in health
to love and to cherish...
until death do us part.
You seem to have that down.
This has been a long time coming.
- And now you, Wayne.
- Uh, everything she just said.
Grace...
no more wasted time.
I wanna spend every day with you.
Every day for the rest of our lives
and... whatever comes after.
Love freely given has no beginning
or end.
Your rings represent
your unending love for each other.
May I have the ring for Grace, please?
Thanks.
Place that ring on Grace's finger
and repeat after me.
I give you this ring as a symbol of my love.
Grace, I give you this ring
as a symbol of my love.
With this ring, I marry you.
With this ring... I marry you.
May we have the ring
for Wayne, please?
- I think you know what to do.
- Yeah.
Wayne, I give you this ring
as a symbol of my love.
With this ring, I marry you.
In as much as the two of you
have made known
your mutual desire
and your consent to be married
by virtue of the authority invested in me
I hereby pronounce you
husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
I'm sorry it's not the fairy tale
you dreamed of.
I'll take the real thing any day.
Hey, guys...
your ride to the hotel is ready.
We have a ride?
We have a ride.
Twenty-one-gun salute formation.
Ready!
Aim!
Fire!
- I think that's our cue.
- Ready!
Aim!
Fire!
Ready!
Aim!
Fire!